investorwords.com 2013-05-19

# Privacy Policy, Disclaimer and Copyright

**Privacy Policy**

We collect no information about our users that is not supplied voluntarily through web forms or e-mail. Any information collected in this manner is never shared with anyone unless expressly requested by the user. We do not sell or reveal user information to anyone. We may at times collect anonymous tracking information to gauge usage patterns and the popularity of specific areas of the site. As with all other information, these data do not leave InvestorGuide.com. Some of this data is gathered through the use of cookies. Cookies may be deactivated by the user at any time. They are not required for any InvestorGuide.com site to function properly. Transparent gifs or pixels may occasionally be used for the same purpose, but these items gather no personal data and have no effect on site use or navigation. 

All of our newsletters are strictly opt-in, meaning that they are sent only to those who have specifically requested to receive them. Unsubscribe instructions are included at the bottom of each issue. Some newsletter issues include advertising, clearly identified as such. By signing up to receive our email newsletters, you also agree to receive occasional email announcements and special offers from our partners. However, no information gathered from newsletter subscribers, including e-mail addresses, is ever shared with or sold to any third-party. We are not responsible for the claims or representations made by advertisers and sponsors.

**Information collected by third-parties**

We may allow third-party companies that use tracking technologies, such as cookies or pixels, to record IP information about users who visit or interact with our website. Our website does not provide any personal information to these third parties. This information allows them to deliver targeted advertisements and gauge their effectiveness. Some of these third-party advertising companies may be advertising networks that are members of the Network Advertising Initiative which offers a single location to opt out of ad targeting from member companies.

**Disclaimer**

Reproduction of the glossary, in whole or in part, is prohibited without the written permission of WebFinance, Inc. However, we do encourage you to mention and link to the site. 

This site is published with the understanding that the publisher is not engaged in rendering legal or investment services. Since each individual's situation is unique, a qualified professional should be consulted before making tax, legal or investment decisions. We make no guarantees as to the accuracy, thoroughness or quality of the information, and are not responsible for errors or omissions. The information provided at this site is neither comprehensive nor appropriate for every individual. Some of the information is relevant only in the U.S., and would differ elsewhere. Some of the glossary terms relate to subjects or investment strategies that might not be appropriate for some individuals. You are strongly cautioned to verify any information before using it for any personal, financial or business purpose. Do not rely solely on what you find here for making investment decisions. This site is provided on the express condition, to which all making use thereof assent, that no liability shall be incurred by WebFinance Inc. or any of its employees. 

We are not responsible for the claims or representations made by advertisers and sponsors. WebFinance Inc. does not endorse or recommend the products or services of any company mentioned on our site. 

Nothing on this site should be construed as an offer or solicitation to buy or sell any products or securities. All investments involve risk. Past performance does not guarantee future results. Investigate before you invest. 

We collect no information about our users that is not supplied voluntarily through web forms or e-mail. Any information collected in this manner is never shared with anyone unless expressly requested by the user. We do not sell or reveal user information to anyone. We may at times collect anonymous tracking information to gauge usage patterns and the popularity of specific areas of the site. As with all other information, these data do not leave InvestorGuide.com. Some of this data is gathered through the use of cookies. Cookies may be deactivated by the user at any time. They are not required for any InvestorGuide.com site to function properly. Transparent gifs or pixels may occasionally be used for the same purpose, but these items gather no personal data and have no effect on site use or navigation. 

All of our newsletters are strictly opt-in, meaning that they are sent only to those who have specifically requested to receive them. Unsubscribe instructions are included at the bottom of each issue. Some newsletter issues include advertising, clearly identified as such. By signing up to receive our email newsletters, you also agree to receive occasional email announcements and special offers from our partners. However, no information gathered from newsletter subscribers, including e-mail addresses, is ever shared with or sold to any third-party. We are not responsible for the claims or representations made by advertisers and sponsors. 

**Copyright©**

InvestorWords is located at http://www.investorwords.com  
Copyright©2012 by WebFinance, Inc. ALL RIGHTS RESERVED.  
Reproduction of all or part of this glossary, in any format, without the written consent of WebFinance, Inc. is prohibited.

**Copyright Complaints**

WebFinance Inc respects the intellectual property of others, and we ask our users to do the same. WebFinance Inc may, in appropriate circumstances and at its discretion, suspend or terminate the access of and take other action against users, subscribers, registrants and account holders who infringe the copyright rights of others.

If you believe that your work has been copied and is accessible on a WebFinance Inc’s website in a way that constitutes copyright infringement, or that the website contains links or other references to another online location that contains material or activity that infringes your copyright rights, you may notify us by providing the following information (as required by the **Online Copyright Infringement Liability Limitation Act of the Digital Millennium Copyright Act, 17 U.S.C. sec. 512** ) to our copyright agent set forth below:

  * A physical or electronic signature of person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed;
  * Identification of the copyrighted work claimed to have been infringed, or if multiple copyrighted works at a single online site are covered by a single notification, a representative list of such works at that site;
  * Identification of the material that is claimed to be infringing or to be the subject of infringing activity and that is to be removed or access to which is to be disabled, and information reasonably sufficient to permit us to locate the material;
  * Information reasonably sufficient to permit us to contact the complaining party, such as an address, telephone number, and if available, an electronic mail address at which the complaining party may be contacted;
  * A statement that the complaining party has a good faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law; and
  * A statement that the information in the notification is accurate, and under penalty of perjury, that the complaining party is authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed

Once notice is given to us, we will expeditiously remove, or disable access to, the material. WebFinance Inc is not required to notify the individual responsible for the allegedly infringing material before it has been removed.

**Copyright Agent**

Thomas Murcko  
10201 Fairfax Blvd, suite 570  
Fairfax, VA 22030  
Phone: (703) 246-9887  
E-mail:
